{
    "question": "23. Man : \"How does it feel if I press here?\u201d    Woman : \"Oh, that hurts.\"\r\nMan : \"I see. You have an appendix. We'll\r\nhave an operation immediately.\"\r\nWhich part of her body hurts?\r\n\r\nA. Nose\r\nB. Ear\r\nC. Eye\r\nD. Throat\r\nE. Stomach\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>E. Stomach</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Appendix = Usus Buntu</p>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>E. Stomach</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>because the womenhave an operation immediately. stomach part</p><p></p><p>may be useful</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "anara-some-new-arrivals-book-via-online-last-sunday-a-bought-871",
            "question": "Anara.... some new arrivals book via online last Sunday    a. bought\r\nb. buys\r\nc. buy\r\nd. buying\r\ne. was buying \u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>a.bought </p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf kalau salah </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Anara.... some new arrivals book via online last Sunday\n</p><p><strong>a. bought</strong>\n</p><p>b. buys\n</p><p>c. buy\n</p><p>d. buying\n</p><p>e. was buying \u200b</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Jawaban dicetak tebal dan menggunakan bentuk Simple Past Tense karena menjelaskan aktivitas kegiatan di masa lampau.</p><p>Simple Past Tense:</p><p>(+) Subject + Verb-2 + Object</p><p>Semoga membantu ya.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "6-in-they-read-a-book-under-a-tree-yes-a-they-are-h-they-wers-581",
            "question": "6 in they read a book under a tree?    Yes\r\na. They are\r\nh. They wers\r\nc. They will\r\nd. They do\r\n7. We can buy ruler in the\r\na. Stationery store\r\nb. Candy store\r\ne. Electronic store\r\nd. Music store\r\n8. Rama: Look at these shoes, Lita,\r\nThey are very nice\r\nLita : Yes?\r\nRama ninety nine thousand rupiah\r\na Of course\r\nb. Sure\r\nc. Don't worry\r\nd. How much are they\r\nThe conversation below for question number 9-11\r\nRoger . Hey, Rudi ! Let's play basketball today, shall we?\r\nRudi : Oh no, not today. Sorry. Maybe tomorrow.\r\nRoger \u00b7 What's the matter?\r\nRudi I'm not feeling very well. I've got a beadache.\r\nRoger; Oh sorry to hear that. Here. Take this. You should take an spirin\r\nRudi\r\n\u2022 Er. Ok.\r\n9. What does Roger want to do ?\r\na. Play basketball\r\nb. Reads book\r\nc. Camping\r\nd. Playing football\r\n10. What does Roger give to Rudi?\r\na. A baskztball\r\nb. An aspirin\r\nC. A sboes\r\nd. A medicine\r\n11. Who take the aspirio ?\r\na Roger\r\nb. Rudi\r\nc. Sinta\r\nd. Budi\r\n12. The students go to school...... (setiap hari)\r\na. Every day\r\nb. Every Sunday\r\nc. Tomorrow\r\nd. Yesterday\r\n13. My living room is not.......(besar), but I am happy.\r\na. Small\r\n6. Big\r\nc. Beautiful\r\nd. Cheap\r\n\r\ntolong di bantu jawabanya\r\ntrimakasih\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>6. a. they are</p><p>7. stationery store</p><p>8. d. how much are they?</p><p>9. a. play basketball</p><p>10. b. an aspirin</p><p>11. b. Rudi</p><p>12. a. every day</p><p>13. b. big</p><p></p><p>semoga terbantu ya\u270c</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "a-person-who-behaves-iii-a-u-a-person-with-bad-manners-someone-wh-469",
            "question": "A person who behaves III a u    A person with bad manners\r\nSomeone who is not very talkative\r\nSomeone who is very tidy\r\nSomeone who is good at learning things\r\nA truthful person who doesn't cheat or st\r\nTask 10\r\nRearrange the jumbled words into a correct sentence!\r\nvery - she-me-is-to-kind\r\n1.\r\n2.\r\nbe-minded-close-don't-So\r\n3.\r\nyoung-she-woman-an-is-energetic\r\nwer\r\n4.\r\nhas - personality-an-she-outgoing\r\n4. Let's associate\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. she is very kind of me</p><p>2. don&#039;t be so close minded</p><p>3. she is an energetic young woman</p><p>4. she has an outgoing personality</p><p></p><p>semoga terbantu, maap kalo salah\u270c</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. very - she-me-is-to-kind</p><p>she is very kind to me</p><p>2. be-minded-close-don&#039;t-So</p><p>don&#039;t be so close minded</p><p>3.young-she-woman-an-is-energetic</p><p>she is an energetic young woman</p><p>4. has - personality-an-she-outgoing</p><p>she has an outgoing personality</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Idk whether its true or not, but  I hope it can help u, gudluck :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "how-did-you-say-to-compare-animal-258",
            "question": "How did you say to compare animal",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>The elephant is bigger than the tiger</p><p></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "exercise-five-give-questions-1-where-the-two-women-lived-323",
            "question": "EXERCISE FIVE    Give questions :-\r\n?\r\n1. Where\r\n?\r\nThe two women lived in the same house.\r\n2. How many\r\nThey each had a child.\r\n?\r\n3. What happened\r\nIt happened that one of the children died one night.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. Where did the two women live?</p><p>2. How many child they have each?</p><p>3. What happened one night?</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p><strong>1. Kalimat dalam </strong><em><strong>past tense</strong></em><strong>, jadi pertanyaan menggunakan kata kerja </strong><em><strong>did </strong></em><strong>setelah kata tanya.</strong></p><p><strong>2. Menanyakan jumlah. Yang menjadi obyek dengan jumlah ditanyakan adalah &#039;a child&#039;. Subyeknya adalah </strong><em><strong>they </strong></em><strong>yang merupakan</strong><em><strong> </strong></em><strong>kata ganti jamak, jadi kata kerja di pertanyaan menggunakan </strong><em><strong>have</strong></em><strong>.</strong></p><p><strong>3. Yang ditanyakan adalah apa, jadi peristiwa yang menjadi jawaban tidak disebutkan di pertanyaan.</strong></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "b-write-ab-or-c-tulislah-ab-atau-c-1-my-hobby-is-me-259",
            "question": "B. Write a,b, or c ( Tulislah a,b atau c)!    1. My hobby is ... (Memasak)\r\n2. Two mother is meaning ...\r\n3. Teacher How are you?\r\nStudent\r\nThank you\r\n4. Anggur is\r\n5. Cat eats\r\n6. I like playing football\r\nFootball is\r\n7. Empat pisang kuning is.\r\n8. Indonesian flag is ..... And\r\n9. Teacher Riri is my English\r\n(Guru)\r\n10. Father is\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p> 1. Cooking</p><p></p><p>2. Step mother / second mother</p><p></p><p>3. I&#039;m fine, thank you</p><p></p><p>4. Grape</p><p></p><p>5. Fish</p><p></p><p>6. Sepakbola</p><p></p><p>7. There are four yellow banana</p><p></p><p>8. Red and white</p><p></p><p>9. Guru</p><p></p><p>10. Ayah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "to-express-sympathy-we-use-a-im-sorry-b-thank-you-c-may-i-d-929",
            "question": "To express sympathy, We use    A. i'm sorry \r\n B. Thank you\r\n C. May I\r\n D. Can you\r\n\r\n Tolong yya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>C) May I</p><p></p><p>Maaf kalau salah :) </p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p></p><p><em><u>C</u></em><em><u>.</u></em><em><u> </u></em><em><u>may</u></em><em><u> </u></em><em><u>i</u></em></p><p></p><p>semoga membantu:)</p><p>maaf kalau salah..</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "write-two-sentences-expressing-what-is-happening-around-you-a-b-378",
            "question": "Write two sentences expressing what is happening around you\r\nA.\r\nB.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. many weddings</p><p>B. always stuck</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1-write-a-procedure-text-akl-how-to-make-a-label-774",
            "question": "1. write a procedure text :\r\nAKL ( how to make a label)\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. tulis teks prosedur :</p><p>AKL (cara membuat label) </p><p></p><p><strong>ini</strong><strong> </strong><strong>terjem</strong><strong>ahan</strong><strong> </strong><strong>nya</strong><strong> </strong><strong>,</strong><strong> </strong><strong>aja</strong><strong> </strong></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-paragraf-dalam-kalimat-kalimat-yang-bentuk-present-perfect-253",
            "question": "Contoh paragraf dalam kalimat-kalimat yang bentuk present perfect tense\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Today is 16th August and tomorrow is my sister\u2019s birthday. Her name is Kristal. I want to give her a surprise. I have talked to some of her friends. They have helped me to prepare a surprising party. We have discussed it since July.</p><p>We are going to celebrate my sister\u2019s birthday in a small restaurant near my house. Our parents have also agreed it. The restaurant has been booked by our parents.</p><p></p><p>What about the birthday present? No worries, I have prepared it too. She loves art very much. I have made a painting for her. I hope she will like it. But I haven\u2019t wrapped the painting because it hasn\u2019t dried yet.</p><p></p><p>Have you ever celebrated someone\u2019s birthday?</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}